Inventory of the John Ehrlichman papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- NIXON ADMINISTRATION FILE, Appendix A - Documents: Files, 1963-1982 (Boxes 1-3)
  - Controls (TT/Sh/E), Food Prices, PR of Inflation, Phase III, P. Peterson, Rinfret, Labor support, Rev. sharing $, sh to Mills / Long, Trade, Monetary, For. Economic issues, World Bank, Cut UN ½, P. Peterson, Mode of departure, Russian Gas Deal, JBC in, others out, Rumsfeld - mistake, Goals of PS (?!) P P?!) trip (13 pages), 1972 December 5
  - Viet Nam Negotiations, HAK instructions (TT/H/E) (Aspen) (3 pages), 1972 December 6
  - Florida lots-Tricia, Sinatra - Bicentennial (TT/H/E), Restaffing (CD?), Viet Nam - HAK, 5:30p. (3 pages), 1972 December 7
  - IRS Grievences, C Clifford never audited (TT/Sh/Webster/E), Hating bureaucrats, Honesty, clean house, Pull files w/o Q-never improper, Sensitive Case Reps, E or Dean, 1:30p (4 pages), 1972 December 7
  - P. Peterson, Rumsfeld (TT E), Griswold (Aspen), Sneed, 9:30 am (3 pages), 1972 December 7
  - Georgia senate race, Herman Talmedge will deal (TT/Campbell/E), Agric. bureauc. go (Aspen), Weinberger conserv. Strategy, HUD dismantled, PR Plan-reorg., Finch-Hamlet, Krogh to Dot etc., *s/cr list - 2 Catholics, Morton temporary - Whitaker in, can't run anything, Interior restaff, Our men in the Depts, orderly control of Govt., Energy, OST - wither, LBJ - RN, Interior's problems (15 pages), 1972 December 7
  - Budget: Sale of Assets (TT/sh/Weinberger), CIA - Schlesinger cuts (Stein/Carlucci/Cole/E), Dod supplemental (Aspen), Dod cuts, OEO - can't cut out-strategy, services, ABA - never WH, Decentralize, 250 bil., Gt. Soc. over, Unemp. 5.2%, Controls justified-, Jobs programs, ZPG, 10 year Plan, "Nations decline when births decline," Who is reproducing? Demographics, Energy & populin projections, RIF, No exec. raises, space cuts, cuts, WH Staff-50% cut (19 pages), 1972 December 7
  - RN view of DOJ (TT/Sneed/E), Ivy League-those frilly games (Aspen), Keep some incompetent blacks, Wash. elite-most hated TT, Burger, Rhenquist, E's leftwingers, Kleindienst creature of DO J, Sneed-Texan-born pol, Recruiting for DO J, Sally Ann Payto 'on crt track' -, 10a (8 pages), 1972 December 8
  - Brenniger not a Catholic (TT/H/E), wasting Krogh, Poor Cabinet, image, PP, Fresh Ideas, Criteria for Cabinet, Anne Armstrong, Georgetown influences-Disraeli & Aristocracy, New N constituency-not suburbia, Only Brennan & I come from working class, Borko & Buchanens survive & become "great nuts", Reagan, Movie for secys, Black women for S/ct, W/G & Chapin, JNM failed, Dean Report-before Xmas-during for. peace action, Chapin leaving, Strachan-H defends, Statement soon-no one in WH but DC & Strachan (8 pages), 1972 December 11
  - Tax/E pol/not Sh, RK note via RMW re/Gray (TT/H/E), Ann Armstrong-Tokenism, Brenniger-mistake, Tokens, Pottinger (4 pages), 1972 December 13
  - Director for FBI, Gray pro & con (TT Kleindenst E), Matt Byrne, Felt the leak, Martha-"sick"-JNM could have prevented W/G, Hoover-no controversy, -died just in time, -the breakfast-strikeout, Football/blackout T.V. (5 pages), 1972 December 18
  - Restaff, secret service chgs. (TT/H/E) (4 pages), 1972 December 18
  - Diary: 2/-4/ (6 pages), 1973
  - Newbould Noye's letter to the TT (Missing pages), 1973 January 17
  - During confirmation (Pat Gray), Gray talks w/me re:, W/G, phone (3 pages), 1973 March 8
  - Brennan, CC running DOL (Sh ph), Appointees (2 pages), 1973 February 12
  - Pat Hill (TT Ph), Belzano (2 pages), 1973 February 19
  - J.B. Connally, El Paso Gas case (C ph), W/G (6 pages), 1973 March 28
  - Sam Ervin, phone conv. re committee leaks, secret mtgs. (Missing pages), 1973 April 2
  - GRAY nomination w/drawn, innocent victim, broken man but not a POW for 7 years. It's all relative (1 page), 1973 April 6
  - Civil settlements, Ervin Leak (J.N. Mitchell phone) (3 pages), 1973 April 11
  - W./G. Report to TT by E (JE) (8 pages), 1973 April 17
  - Tape/nb - TT & Dk Moore (7 pages), 1973 April 19
  - Rules 2nd Mting (Howard Baker phone), Ervin attacks on TT (Missing Contents pages), 1973 April 13
  - Re: committee's procedural rules (Ervin/Baker phone) (7 pages), 1973 April 16
  - Hunt & Liddy (Memo-Silbert to H. Petersen), broke in Ellsbergs psych. (1 page), 1973 April 16
  - Macgruder-press (C. Colson phone) (5 pages), 1973 April 20
  - Colson-W/G, notes of mtg. w/ CC (3 pages), 1973 April 23
  - Ziegler delivers the message:, H & E must go (Ziegler), Dispute re what JBC says (H & E) (6 pages), 1973 April 25
  - What JBC said, LEAVE OF ABSENCE (TT/H/E), JNM MAY LIE ABOUT E, ROGERS, H LISTEN TO TAPES OF TT/DEAN, Fire Dean-no immunity, Clemency, H Peterson-coddling Dean-wait, Leave for all (12 pages), 1973 April 25
  - Kleindienst resign, Richardson (Phone-Ziegler), Dean, Mitchell 4/15 or 4/16, Colson 4/16 - Dean (8 pages), 1973 April 30
  - Re Ellsberg break in -, Did I know sooner? (TT/E), E-nod, TT: If so, I don't recall (3 pages), 1973 May 2
  - Reports, statements, charts, military cables, memoranda and letters relating to General William Westmoreland, CBS, and enemy force estimates during the Vietnam war, 1963-1982
- AUDIOVISUAL FILE, Appendix B - John Ehrlichman Media Tapes, 1971-1978 (Boxes 4-17)
  Audiotapes relating to Watergate, primarily recordings of news broadcasts. Arranged chronologically; see Appendix B for detailed box list (prepared by the Archives of Artists of New Mexico and the Southwest).
  - "Impeachment," Mike Wallace/John Lofton/, Helen Thomas/Anthony Lewis/, Daniel Ellsberg, 2 sides, undated (Box 4, Tape 1)
  - Judge John J. Sirica, TV Capsules, undated (Tape 2)
  - Les Whitten, JE-DE NEW (?!), undated (Tape 3)
  - Side 1: Hunt/Dean Segs., Side 2: Sen. Frank Church on CIA, undated (Tape 4)
  - The Cooney's and Guests, WMCA Radio (Talk Show) on RN/Ford/Impeachment/etc., 2 sides, undated (Tape 5)
  - John Ehrlichman, CBS Radio - Washington Week, 1971 January 30 (Tape 6)
  - J. E., on CBS Television, 1971 April 29 (Tape 7)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, Part Two/ABC and NET, 1973 July 24 (Tape 8)
  - J. E., television, CBS TV/NBC TV/ABC, Hearings: Start: NBC TV/NET TV, Side 2: J. E., CBS TV Special (hour) 10 p.m., 1973 July 24 (Tape 9)
  - J. E., "Hearings" NET/NBC TV - Comments: 2 p.m. start/recess, Side 2: J. E., "Hearings" Recess and End, Comments: NET/NBC TV, 1973 July 24 (Tape 10)
  - J. E. (Box 1), Side 1: Watergate Hearings (Noon), Track 1: WNET, Track 3: CBS, Side 2: Track 1: NET TV, Track 3: CBS TV, 1973 July 24 (Tape 11)
  - J. E. (Box 2), Watergate Hearings, Track 1: NET, Track 3: Network, 2 sides, 1973 July 24-25 (Tape 12)
  - J. E. (Box 3), "Hearings" (Final part), Side 2: CBS TV Special 10 p.m., TV News Capsules added, 1973 July 25-26 (Tape 13)
  - J. E., "Hearings" Side 1: 2 p.m. start/recess, Side 2: NET/CBS TV Comments, "Recess" Ervin Interview/Aide Interview, 1973 July 25 (Tape 14)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, Track 1: NET/Track 3: NET, 2 sides, 1973 July 25 (Tape 15)
  - J. E., "Hearings" NET/CBS TV Comments:, Start/Noon..., Side 2: Attorney Wilson Comments, 1973 July 25 (Tape 16)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings (Part 2), 2 p.m. session, 2 sides, 1973 July 26 (Box 5, Tape 17)
  - J. E., "Hearings" 2 sides - ABC/NET, 1973 July 26 (Tape 18)
  - J. E., "Hearings" 2 sides, Track 1 - NET, Track 3 - ABC, 1973 July 26 (Tape 19)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, NET/ABC TV Comments, Start/Noon/Recess/End, 2 sides, 1973 July 26 (Tape 20)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, 2 sides, 1973 July 27 (Tape 21)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, 2 sides, 1973 July 27 (Tape 22)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, 2 sides, 1973 July 27 (Tape 23)
  - J. E., "Hearings" Comments: NET/NBC TV, 2 sides (Parts 1 and 2), 1973 July 27 (Tape 24)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, 2 sides, 1973 July 27 (Tape 25)
  - J. E., TV News Capsules, Side 2: "Washington Week Review," NET TV, RN/JE/Cambodia/etc., 1973 July 27-28 (Tape 26)
  - J. E., "Hearings" (Part 3) Comments by NET/NBC TV, Side 2: Author FBI Agent, Connors on RN/JE/etc., NBC Radio 8 to 9 p.m., 1973 July 27 (Tape 27)
  - "Watergate" CBS TV Special 8 p.m., NBC TV Special 9 p.m., 2 sides, 1973 July 27 (Tape 28)
  - TV capsules, 2 sides, 1973 July 27-30 (Tape 29)
  - J. E., "Hearings" NET/CBS TV Start/Noon/End, JE Interview, 2 sides, (Network TV News Comments on JE at end of Side 2), 1973 July 30 (Tape 30)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, Part One: NET and Network, Track 1: NET/Track 3: Network, 2 sides, 1973 July 30 (Tape 31)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, Part 3/NET and Network, Side 2: H. R. H., 1973 July 30 (Tape 32)
  - J. E./H. R. H., Watergate Hearings, NOTE: Final part of HRH is midway on Side 2, Track 3/after Network discussion, 1973 July 30 (Box 6, Tape 33)
  - "The Advocates" "Should the President Be Impeached," NET TV, 2 sides, 1973 December 9 (Tape 34)
  - Side 1: Lowell Weicker, ABC TV, Side 2: TV News Capsules on RN - Taxes, 1973 December 9 (Tape 35)
  - WPIX TV on Juror/Debate, 10 p.m., 1974 January 2 (Tape 36)
  - Side 1: G. Gordon Liddy, "60 Minutes" Side 2: NBC TV Report '74-75, 1974 January 5 (Tape 37)
  - TV capsules, 2 sides, 1974 January 11-15 (Tape 38)
  - Egil Korgh, "60 Minutes" (January 27) and other TV News from January 24-25, 2 sides, 1974 January 24-27 (Tape 39)
  - Side 1: TV capsules, 1974 January 28-29 (Tape 40)
  - Grand Jury Indictments, TV News Capsules/Specials, 2 sides, 1974 March 1 (Tape 41)
  - TV Capsules, RN/Vesco/JM/Chapin/etc., Wilbur Mills Interview, 2 sides, 1974 March 1 (Tape 42)
  - TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 March 2-3 (Tape 43)
  - TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 March 4 (Tape 44)
  - TV Sound Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 March 5-6 (Tape 45)
  - President Richard M. Nixon's Press Conference, Comments on Side 2, 1974 March 6 (Tape 46)
  - Side 1: Radio WMCA Bob Grant talks with Anthony Lewis of New York Times, CBS TV a.m. Panel Discussion, Metromedia/WPIX RV, Side 2: TV Capsules, CBS TV/ABC TV/NBC TV Networks, a.m. TV: Douglas - Voorhees/Govs, 1974 March 7 (Tape 47)
  - Side 1: "Washington Week Review" (March 8), NET TV, Side 2: TV Capsules, "60 Minutes" Kilpatrick - von Hoffman on RN Aides (March 9), 1974 March 8-9 (Tape 48)
  - J. E., TV, 2 sides, 1974 March 11 (Box 7, Tape 49)
  - J. E., TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 March 12-13 (Tape 50)
  - Side 1: Vice President Ford, CBS TV a.m. Interview on RN and News spots, Side 2: Networks:, Ford/Julie/Cubans/JM/Woods: CBS, Ford - HK/Mills/Shultz/RN/Cubans/JM/JC: ABC, Bebe/Woods/Cubans/RN/House/JM/Pat: NBC, 1974 March 14 (Tape 51)
  - Side 1: Schoumacher AB Radio, Side 2: WMCA Phones/RN at '01 Opry', 1974 March 17 (Tape 52)
  - Sirica/JM/RN/Buchanan, TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 March 18 (Tape 53)
  - President Richard M. Nixon, NAB Press Conference, Houston, Texas, Side 2: Comments, 1974 March 19 (Tape 54)
  - Side 1: TV networks, Side 2: Buckley statement/and a.m. TV, 1974 March 19 (Tape 55)
  - TV Capsules, Side 1: Roy Cohn on NET for RN and news capsules added, Side 2: RN/House/JE/JM/Bebe/etc., 1974 March 20-21 (Tape 56)
  - Side 1: Howard Baker "Issues" (March 24), "Washington Week in Review" NET (March 22), TV News Capsules (March 22), Side 2: TV News Capsules, Conyers/Wilson/Appeal/Albert/Bebe/, ABA Smith Interview/Halpern Tap/RN/, GSA/CBS Radio "Washington Week"/etc., 1974 March 22-24 (Tape 57)
  - 2 Sides: Carl Albert NET TV, Side 2: Interview, 1974 March 25 (Tape 58)
  - TV Capsules, Grand Jury Report/JM-Dean/, Court/oil-CBS/ABC/and NBC TV, 2 sides, 1974 March 26 (Tape 59)
  - Side 1: NET TV "Behind the Lines," The Media and the Presidency, Side 2: TV Capsules, 1974 March 28 (Tape 60)
  - Side 1: TV (March 30); CBS: (Rather) Ford/GOP/Percy/HK, RN - Taxes/Schorr on IRS Mail - RN/, JE/RN - Welfare/Zumwatt/Migrants/P, Energy/Dems, NBC: HK Weds/HK/Ford/RN - Taxes/, Butz/Beef/RN - Hearst, ABC: Reasoner Report: "Arabs," Radio: RN - Taxes/JE/Percy/JE/Taxes/, Dems/HK/Dems/Ford/Dayan/Sadat/HK/, Ford/Taxes/Ford/JE/Jessup/HK/HK, Side 2: "Washington Week Review," NET TV: Discussing HK/RN - Jaworski/ (march 29); Congress/HHH/Milk, HHH Interview "Today"/a.m. TV News, TV News segments on Networks for March 29,, 7 p.m., 1974 March 29-30 (Tape 61)
  - Side 1: Wilbur Mills "Issues" "World This Week" CBS (April 7); Side 2: "Washington Week in Review "NET (April 5), 1974 April 5 and 7 (Tape 62)
  - Side 1: "Merv" TV, Frank Mankiewicz/Herb Klein/Father, McLaughlin Guests on RN, Side 2: IRS Alexander on Meet Press, Rep. John Rhodes on "Face Nation," Nobelsville on RB/von H-Kilpatrick/Bebe, 1974 April 6 (Tape 63)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules (April 9); Side 2: Lowell Weicker Testimony and News Capsules/JE (April 8), 1974 April 8-9 (Tape 64)
  - TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 April 10 (Box 8, Tape 65)
  - Side 1: TV capsules, Side 2: Helen Thomas/McClendon, 1974 April 15 (Tape 66)
  - J. E., Side 1: TV Capsules (April 17), Side 2: TV Capsules (April 16), 1974 April 16-17 (Tape 67)
  - TV capsules, 2 sides, 1974 April 22 (Tape 68)
  - TV Sound Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 April 23-24 (Tape 69)
  - Side 1: President Richard M. Nixon talk Comments: CBS TV/ABC TV/NBC TV CBS Radio Rangel/Julie; Side 2: Comments: NET TV-Rewhitt-Hess/ Railsback; WBAI FM/WINS Radio/ Schoenbrun comment, 1974 April 29 (Tape 70)
  - "The Day After the President's Talk on the Transcripts," 2 sides, 1974 April 30 (Tape 71)
  - Presidential Transcript (2nd day after), 2 sides, 1974 May 1 (Tape 72)
  - Transcripts...News, 2 sides, 1974 May 2-3 (Tape 73)
  - Side 1: NET TV; "Washington Week in Review" Nets: CBS: TV News, Side 2: CBS TV Continued:, ABC TV/NBC TV:, Carson "Raps "RN, Radio, 1974 May 3-4 (Tape 74)
  - Side 1: "Oil" JE/ABC TV; "Face Nation" James St. Clair; "Issues" Alexander Haig; Steward Alsop "Bob Grant" Radio, Side 2: "Impeachment" WMCA Radio; JM-Stans trial report; Reps. Smith and Fish on RN, 1974 May 5 (Tape 75)
  - TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 May 6-7 (Tape 76)
  - Tapes/Transcripts, Side 1: TV Capsules, Side 2: "Impeachment" NET TV, "Straight Talk" Sen. Ted Kennedy, 1974 May 8 (Tape 77)
  - Side 1: Alger Hiss Interview NET TV, Side 2: CBS TV/ABC TV Commentaries on Judiciary Session #1 (Live), 1974 May 8 (Tape 78)
  - Side 1: Jack Anderson/Carson, TV News: Metromedia/WPIX, Dr. McLaughlin - Bob Grant phone call, a.m. TV, Side 2: TV Capsules CBS/ABC, Judiciary Live NBC Session #1, 1974 May 9 (Tape 79)
  - TV/Radio capsules, Transcripts/RN - Box #1, 1974 May 10-11 (Tape 80)
  - Side 1: E. Howard Hunt/Buckley, Side 2: "Washington Week in Review" NET Box #2, 1974 May 12 (Box 9, Tape 81)
  - RN/Transcripts, etc., TV Capsules: 2 sides, 1974 May 13 (Tape 82)
  - TV capsules, RN/transcripts, 1974 May 14 (Tape 83)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules (Nets) (May 15); RN/House/Tapes (May 16); Side 2: a.m. TV (May 17); Judiciary/RN/JE/Bebe/etc., a.m. TV RN/Tapes/House (May 15); Robert Strauss "Straight Talk," NET TV, 1974 May 15-17 (Tape 84)
  - RN/Transcripts, etc., TV Coverages, 2 sides, 1974 May 17 (Tape 85)
  - RN/House/Sirica/J, RN Radio Talk/Rodino Interview NET TV, 2 sides, 1974 May 20 (Tape 86)
  - TV capsules, RN/House, 1974 May 21-22 (Tape 87)
  - Side 1: Korff-others "51st State" NET TV, WPIX: RN tapes/Doar; Metro: HK/Abend-Riesel on Mideast/RN; Doar/McL/RN/EK/McCord/McL/HK, Side 2: Ted Koppel on Barry Gray discuss HK Nets: CBS/NBC/ABC on RN-tapes/House, 1974 May 23 (Tape 88)
  - Side 1: Sen. Byrd "Face" (May 26); ABC Smith "Meet Press," a.m. TV (May 27); Side 2: Washington Week Review/NET TV (May 24); a.m.: Duke/Rather/RN/Saxbe/RN/, Perspective on Ford/H/Duke/K-von H./, Burns/RN/Byrd/Poll/etc., 1974 May 24-27 (Tape 89)
  - TV capsules, Side 1: May 27-28, Side 2: Barry Gray Radio, 1974 May 27-28 (Tape 90)
  - Side 1: Riesel-Abend on K's-RN; TV Capsules, Side 2: Greenspan/Snyder "Tomorrow" NBC and TV Capsules, 1974 May 29-30 (Tape 91)
  - TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 May 31-June 2 (Tape 92)
  - TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 June 3 (Tape 93)
  - TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 June 4 (Tape 94)
  - TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 June 5-6 (Tape 95)
  - TV Capsules, Networks/Gesell/JE/RN House/etc., Side 2: "Washington Week Review," 2 sides, 1974 June 7 (Tape 96)
  - RN Departs on Mideast Tour, JE/Gesell/etc., 2 sides, 1974 June 10 (Box 10, Tape 97)
  - TV Sound Capsules, RN-Cairo/JE/HK/etc., 1974 June 11-12 (Tape 98)
  - President in Egypt/and other news, Side 1: TV capsules, Side 2: Jeb Magruder with Dick Cavett, 1974 June 13 (Tape 99)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules, RN-Mideast/House/JE/HK/etc., Side 2: "Washington Week Review," and a.m. TV, JE, etc., 1974 June 14 (Tape 100)
  - TV Capsules, Woodward and Bernstein Interview, 2 sides, 1974 June 18-19 (Tape 101)
  - TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 June 21-23 (Tape 102)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules (Nets), RN-Brussels/HJ/HK/JE/Mideast;, Side 2: TV a.m. RN Brussels/House/etc., 1974 June 26 (Tape 103)
  - Side 1: TV, RN Arrival in Moscow NBC/ABC Live, Mike Mansfield Interview; Side 2: a.m. TV CBS etc.: RN/House, JE/etc., 1974 June 27 (Tape 104)
  - J. E., 2 sides, 1974 June 25-28 (Tape 105)
  - Side 1: "Update "Watergate," "Washington Week in Review" NET TV, RN News Capsules, Side 2: John McLaughlin ABC TV, Marchetti/CIA "Today," TV News Capsules, 1974 June 28 (Tape 106)
  - TV Capsules, Colson "Today" Interview added, 2 sides, 1974 June 30-July 3 (Tape 107)
  - Side 1: JE-TV (July 3); a.m. and p.m. (July 4); Colson-"Today," (July 5); Side 2: Colson (Part Two) (July 5); "Washington Week Review" NET, 1974 July 3-5 (Tape 108)
  - TV Capsules, JE/RN/Colson Interviews, 2 sides, 1974 July 8-9 (Tape 109)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules; Side 2: TV Composite, etc., 1974 July 10-11 (Tape 110)
  - TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 July 12 (Tape 111)
  - Side 1: TV; CBS: Watergate Report/JE/RN Ford, NBC: RN/Watergate Report/, "Washington Week" CBS Radio, Side 2: Face the Nation, Lowell Weicker - Guest, CBS TV, 1974 July 13-14 (Tape 112)
  - "Sunday" NBC TV, Woodward-Bernstein, 2 sides, 1974 July 14 (Box 11, Tape 113)
  - Woodward and Bernstein with William F. Buckley, 2 sides, 1974 July 14 (Tape 114)
  - Side 1: JE, Side 2: "Tomorrow" Jarrell/Brocaw, Interviews on RN, 1974 July 15-16 (Tape 115)
  - TV Capsules, RN/JE/St. Clair/Tape/etc., 1974 July 18 (Tape 116)
  - Side 1: Ken Clawson "Tomorrow"; CBS TV Special "Impeachment"; Side 2: NET TV Special/Panel; Korff "Today" and CBS TV a.m., 1974 July 18 (Tape 117)
  - Side 1: Track, TV: CBS: Doar/RN/Cyprus:, ABC and NBC also; Side 2: "Washington Week Review"; CBS: House/C/Doar/Z/Tapes, NBC: C/Doar/Tapes-RN/Ford/etc., 1974 July 19-20 (Tape 118)
  - Side 1: James McCord "Tomorrow" NBC TV, Side 2: TV News: Hogan-Burch/etc., 1974 July 23 (Tape 119)
  - TV Capsules, Court Decision/St. Clair Statement, House/Comments 3 Nets at 7 p.m.:, and a.m. TV, 2 sides, 1974 July 24 (Tape 120)
  - Side 1: TV; Theodore White/Latta interviews: News: NBC: House/ St. Clair/House/Miller/RN/Pro RN/ Tower-Brooke interviews; CBS: House/Ford/Hart comment/House/, Side 2: Reports on court decision. a.m. TV RN/Galbraith interview/House: NET-CBS comments on House hearings; Maraziti and Latta live talks, 1974 July 25 (Tape 121)
  - TV capsules: Court/House/Jaworski/Sirica/ Impeach RN/L.A. Talk/comments, 1974 July 25 (Tape 122)
  - Side 1: TV; CBS: House/Sirica/RN/Poll/, Sevareid on RN, NBC: House/Poll/Ford/Sirica, ABC: House/Ford/Sirica/Smith-RN:, House Hearings Comments; Side 2: NET/ABC TV Comments on Saturday, House Hearings:, Live Vote on Article 1:, CBS TV: Cronkite/Sevareid/Mudd, 1974 July 26-27 (Tape 123)
  - Side 1: Rep. Thornton-Butler (July 28); On Face the Nation, "Meet Press" Chas. Black Prof. on Court-RN, Rep./Railsback Interview Today (July 26); Charles Sandman Today, a.m. CBS TV: House/Baker/Court, Side 2: "Newsmaker" CBS TV (July 28); Sen. Jacob Javits, "Issues" Sen. Robert Byrd, a.m. TV RN $/House (July 26), 1974 July 26 and 28 (Tape 124)
  - TV Capsules, Networks/a.m. TV/ABA Smith Interview/etc., 2 sides, 1974 July 29 (Tape 125)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules, CBS: House/Rhodes/Tapes/etc., ABC: House/RN-Tapes/HP/Reasoner Says, NBC: House/RN-Tapes/Dems. Brinkley Says, Interviews: Byrd/Sandman/Wiggins, Side 2: House Windup/NBC/NET Comments, a.m. TV: McClery/House/Ford/RN/JC/Ford/, Hart on Impeachment, PUX: House/Tapes/House, Metromedia: House/Abend on RN (Tape 126)
  - TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1974 July 31 (Tape 127)
  - Side 2: JE/House/RN/Tapes/Koroff/, Ford/Goldwater/House Interviews/Vox Pop RN, Side 1: TV Capsules, CBS: House/RN/Morton/Butterfield/S/C, ABC: RN/JC/Inflation/Smith, NBC: House/RN/Poll/Arends/Ford/JC/$, a.m. TV: House/RN/Pat B./ Burger/JE/JC/HJ, Dole Interviews on "Today"/RN, CBS: House/Montoya/Ford/Tapes/Senate/Burger, Javits Interview: BG/Wallace/Hogan/House/, Fish Jr./Rhodes, 1974 August 1 (Tape 128)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules, CBS: Dean/Tapes/RN/COL./C, NBC: Dean/Tapes/HHH/COL./Mideast, ABC: Dean/Tapes/RN/House/RN/Rhodes, COL/HHH/Railsback-Mezvinsky/R/, a.m. TV: House/Dean/RN/RN/Vox/, Russell Train Interview, CBS: Dean/House/Senate/RN, Side 2: "Washington Week in Review," Discuss: RN-House-Rhodes/Senate/Cyprus/Greece, a.m. TV: Detoledano-Braden on RN/$/Hart/RN/, Jordan/Dean/COL/Japan, ABX: RN/Metro: Dean/WPIX/Dean/RN/$/Meany/, Dean/Grant on RN/RN/HHH on RN, 1974 August 2 (Box 12, Tape 129)
  - TV/Radio, CBS: Ford/House/RN, NBC: RN/Ford/MM/Hogan, "Washington Week" CBS Radio, Reasoner: Impeachment Politics, WMCA phones/McCourt/Grant on RN, 2 sides, 1974 August 3 (Tape 130)
  - TV Capsules, News on RN/von Hoffman-Kilpatrick, Washington Post-Bradlee, Grahm....World This Week/Rush on Kup's Show, 2 sides, 1974 August 4 (Tape 131)
  - a.m. TV, Pest/RN/Tapes/Allen Interview/Paris on RN, RN/Rhodes/RN/Ford/Hart-Kempton on RN tapes/, Rules/Tokyo-London/Sandman, 2 sides, 1974 August 5 (Tape 132)
  - RN Flash/Statement/Networks, Radio-TV-Interviews, 2 sides, 1974 August 5 (Tape 133)
  - TV capsules, 1974 August 7 (Tape 134)
  - TV capsules, Side 1: Networks on RN, Side 2: President Nixon's talks, 1974 August 8 (Tape 135)
  - Side 1: TV news: RN/Ford/comments, Side 2: CBS TV special RN-Ford; "Washington Week in Review" NET RN-Ford, 1974 August 9 (Tape 136)
  - TV capsules: JE/RN/Ford, 2 sides, 1974 August 12 (Tape 137)
  - Side 1: Ford's press conference, Side 2: TV news, 1974 August 28 (Tape 138)
  - TV Capsules, Ford/RN/JE, 2 sides, 1974 September 10 (Tape 139)
  - JOHN EHRLICHMAN, ----Trial----, 2 sides, 1974 October 1-21 (Tape 140)
  - J. E., -----Trial-----, 2 sides, 1974 October 18-November 8 (Tape 141)
  - J. E., 2 sides, 1974 November 11-26 (Tape 142)
  - J. E., 2 sides, 1974 November 27-December 6 (Tape 143)
  - "Verdict" TV-Radio Capsules, 2 sides (Box #1), 1974 December 1 (Tape 144)
  - J. E., -----Trial-----, 2 sides, 1974 December 9-27 (Box 13, Tape 145)
  - "Verdict" Side 1: JOHN EHRLICHMAN "Today," Interview (Box #2), 1975 January 1-2 (Tape 146)
  - "Verdict," "Washington Week Review" NET, Agronsky and Company NET, 2 sides, 1975 January 2-4 (Tape 147)
  - Judge John J. Sirica, TV Capsules: "Release,", 1975 January 8 (Tape 148)
  - "Sirica" TV, 1975 January 9 (Tape 149)
  - Side 1: Sirica (January 10-11); Side 2: Magruder "Face Nation" (January 12), 1975 January 10-12 (Tape 150)
  - Side 1: "Roundtable" CIA, Side 2: Dean/Magruder..., 1975 January 15-16 (Tape 151)
  - Javits; CIA/FBI, 1975 January 19-20 (Tape 152)
  - Side 1: CIA/Agee "Tomorrow" (January 29); Jack Anderson/CIA, Side 2: Magruder's "Tomorrow" (January 28), etc., 1975 January 28-29 (Tape 153)
  - Side 1: Watergate Jury/Mike Douglas, CIA etc..., Roundtable "Jews in American Politics," Side 2: "CIA" Tomorrow NBC TV, 1975 February 6 (Tape 154)
  - Charles Colson, TV Capsules, Ron Ziegler Interview, 1975 February 7 (Tape 155)
  - Side 1: Jack Anderson/Gregory NET, Side 2: Magruder's/Mike Douglas, 1975 February 11 (Tape 156)
  - Judge John J. Sirica, Watergate Sentencing, 1975 February 21 (Tape 157)
  - JOHN EHRLICHMAN, TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1975 February 23-24 (Tape 158)